Facilities Management Department fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- General office files, 1963 - 1984; F-11-1; 7.68 m of textual records
  - Field and site meetings and deficiency tests, 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-7; 8 cm of textual records
    - Men's Residence (20-060-5), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - President's Residence (20-060-6), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - Women's Residence (20-060-7), 1965 - 1967; F-11-1-7-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-14)
    - Science Complex (20-060-8), 1966; F-11-1-7-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-14)
    - Science Complex (20-060-8), 1966; F-11-1-7-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-14)
    - Theatre (20-060-9), 1964 - 1966; F-11-1-7-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-14)
  - General constructions files, 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-8; 5 cm of textual records
    - General, Site Office Memos (20-070-7), 1964 - 1965; F-11-1-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-14)
      Access review (Jun 13, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (1) that contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (employment history). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - Central Heating System (20-080-1), 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-14)
    - Control Air Supply (20-080-2), 1964 - 1965; F-11-1-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-14)
    - Leases (20-150-1), 1964; F-11-1-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
    - Reports - Construction Progress Reports (20-180-1), 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
      Access review (Jun 13, 2022) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
    - Reports - Work Order correspondence (20-180-2), 1966; F-11-1-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
  - Land, 1963 - 1971; F-11-1-9; 10 cm of textual records
    - Alternatives to Burnaby Mountain (20-120-1), 1963; F-11-1-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-14)
      Reviewed for personal or confidential information on August 19, 2021 (ML/RM/RD). No restricted information identified.
    - Burnaby Mountain (20-120-2), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-9-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-14)
    - Acquisition - Private Land (20-120-3), 1963 - 1965; F-11-1-9-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-14)
      Restricted in whole
      Reviewed for personal or confidential information on August 19, 2021 (ML/RM/RD). Identified legal advice throughout the file; restricted under s.14 of FIPPA.
    - Acquisition - Land from Burnaby, Vancouver, Crown (20-120-4), 1963 - 1968; F-11-1-9-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-14)
      Reviewed for personal or confidential information on August 31, 2021 (ML/SM/RM/PH). No restricted information identified.
    - Site Drainage (20-120-6), 1964 - 1965; F-11-1-9-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-14)
    - Surveys and Development (20-120-7), 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-9-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-14)
    - Top Soil (20-120-8), 1964 - 1966; F-11-1-9-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
    - Townsite (20-120-9), 1964 - 1966; F-11-1-9-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
    - Water and Sewer Easement (20-120-10), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-9-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
      Restricted
      Access review (Feb 16, 2023) – File includes records that contain restricted information (legal advice). File restricted in whole, but may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - Centennial Trail (20-120-11), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-9-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
    - Lower Mainland Arch. Assoc. (20-120-13), 1967 - 1971; F-11-1-9-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
  - Parking lots and roads, 1963 - 1978; F-11-1-10; 11 cm of textual records
    - Access Roads (20-185-1), 1963 - 1966; F-11-1-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
    - Access Roads (20-185-1), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-10-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
    - Parking Lots Volume I (20-185-2), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-10-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
    - 1000 Car Park (20-185-3), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-10-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
    - North Face Access - Funicular Railway (52-30), 1970 - 1971; F-11-1-10-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Parking and Roads - Parking Structure (52-31), 1973 - 1974; F-11-1-10-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-29)
    - Parking Lots and Roads - General (74-01), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-10-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-59)
    - General #2 (74-01), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-10-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-59)
    - Parking Lot 'B' - Extension 2 (74-03), 1976 - 1977; F-11-1-10-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-59)
    - Parking Lot 'B' - Extension (74-03), 1977; F-11-1-10-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-59)
    - Administration Building Parking Lot (74-04), 1977; F-11-1-10-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-59)
  - Water and site services, 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-11; 1 cm of textual records
    - Water and site services - water and sewer (20-230-1), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
  - Contracts, 1965 - 1967; F-11-1-12; 3 cm of textual records
    - Contracts and Agreements - Garbage (30-030-5), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-12-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
    - Contracts and Agreements - Janitorial (30-030-6), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-12-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
    - Contractual Correspondence - Elevators Maintenance (30-031-4), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-12-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-15)
    - Contractual Correspondence - Window Cleaning (30-031-15), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-12-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
  - Miscellaneous subject files, 1963 - 1984; F-11-1-13; 18 cm of textual records
    BC Tel; BC Hydro; Food Services; School of Communication; City of Burnaby. Fire Department
    - Electrical/Gas and Power Service (30-050-1), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-13-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Materials and Supplies - Building Requirements [Fencing on Burnaby Mt.] (30-055-4), 1966; F-11-1-13-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Food Services - Student Cafeteria (30-065-4), 1966; F-11-1-13-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Food Services - General (30-065-5), 1965; F-11-1-13-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Fire Prevention - Fire Instructions [Burnaby Fire Dept], 1967; F-11-1-13-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Furnishings and Fixtures and Equipment - Equipment [AQ Millwork] (30-067-1), 1964; F-11-1-13-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Furnishings and Fixtures and Equipment - Elevators (30-067-3), 1967; F-11-1-13-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Misc. - Channel 8 Water Service (30-135-1), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-13-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Telephones - Telecommunications (30-200-5), 1963; F-11-1-13-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Accidents (150-01), 1968; F-11-1-13-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-36)
    - BC Hydro (150-15), 1966 - 1970; F-11-1-13-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-36)
    - BC Tel (150-20), 1969 - 1974; F-11-1-13-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-36)
    - Signage [Extended Service Report] (110-08), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-13-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
    - Energy Conservation (110-09), 1974 - 1978; F-11-1-13-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
    - Complaints (110-11), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-13-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
    - Client/Architect Agreements (110-13), 1972 - 1978; F-11-1-13-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
    - Construction Contract Requirements (110-15), 1972 - 1978; F-11-1-13-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
    - Construction Insurance Payments (110-17), 1977; F-11-1-13-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
    - Space Management System (110-18), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-13-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
    - Pyramid Installation (110-20), 1978 - 1979; F-11-1-13-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
    - Communications Department: Antenna (110-21), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-13-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
    - University Club - Part A (110-22), 1969 - 1978; F-11-1-13-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
    - University Club - Part B (110-22), 1969 - 1978; F-11-1-13-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
    - University Club - Part A (110-22), 1980 - 1984; F-11-1-13-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
    - University Club - Part B (110-22), 1980 - 1984; F-11-1-13-0-25 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
  - Budget, 1971 - 1978; F-11-1-14; 4 cm of textual records
    - Capital Priorities Fall 1971 (90-04), 1971 - 1972; F-11-1-14-0-1 (Archival box - small 11-19)
    - Auditing (12-30), 1971; F-11-1-14-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
    - Capital Projects and Capital Priorities #2 (12-07) file missing, 1978; F-11-1-14-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-37)
  - Committees, 1968 - 1981; F-11-1-15; 23 cm of textual records
    Architects Committee; Administration Committee; South Court Lounge Committee; Physical Plant and Planning Review Committee; University Safety Committee; President's Committee for Disabled Students; University Review Committee; Management Review Committee; Committee for Renaming Campus Facilities
    - Committees - General (14-01), 1968 - 1974; F-11-1-15-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
    - Architects' Committee (14-40), 1968 - 1972; F-11-1-15-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
    - Administration Committee (14-06), 1971 - 1973; F-11-1-15-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
    - Administration Committee (14-06), 1973 - 1974; F-11-1-15-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
    - South Court Lounge Committee (14-10), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-15-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
    - Physical Plant and Planning Review Committee (14-40), 1974; F-11-1-15-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
    - University Safety Committee (14-41), 1975; F-11-1-15-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
    - General (14-01), 1978; F-11-1-15-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-37)
    - Administration (14-02), 1975 - 1976; F-11-1-15-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-37)
    - Administration (14-02), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-15-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-37)
    - Administration (14-02), 1978; F-11-1-15-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-37)
    - Physical Plant and Planning - Review (14-04), 1975 - 1977; F-11-1-15-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-37)
    - University Safety (14-05), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-15-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-37)
    - University Safety (14-05), 1979 - 1981; F-11-1-15-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-37)
    - Parking (14-06), 1976; F-11-1-15-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-37)
    - Physical Plant and Planning - Safety (14-07), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-15-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-37)
    - President Committee for Disabled Students (14-08), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-15-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-38)
    - University Review Committee (14-11), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-15-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-38)
    - Management Review Committee (14-12), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-15-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-38)
    - Committee to Rename Campus Facilities (14-15), 1977; F-11-1-15-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-38)
  - Government, 1972 - 1979; F-11-1-16; 10 cm of textual records
    British Columbia. Department of Highways; City of Burnaby. Fire Department; City of Port Moody; Universities Council of British Columbia; Simon Fraser University Urban Village
    - Department of Highways (16-02), 1972; F-11-1-16-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
    - Burnaby Fire Department (16-03), 1972; F-11-1-16-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
    - Universities Council (16-03), 1974 - 1976; F-11-1-16-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
    - City of Port Moody (16-05), 1974 - 1976; F-11-1-16-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
    - City of Port Moody (16-02), 1975 - 1979; F-11-1-16-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-38)
    - Universities Council (16-03), 1977; F-11-1-16-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-38)
    - Universities Council (16-03), 1978; F-11-1-16-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-38)
    - Centennial Pavilion and Water Supply (16-05), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-16-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-38)
    - Canadian Urban Demonstration Project (16-07), 1975; F-11-1-16-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-38)
  - Other departments at SFU, 1968 - 1974; F-11-1-17; 2 cm of textual records
    Office of the Vice-President, Administration; Human Resources
    - Vice-President Administration [18-06], 1968 - 1974; F-11-1-17-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
    - Personnel Department (18-26), 1972; F-11-1-17-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-20)
  - Physical Plant and Planning, 1965 - 1979; F-11-1-18; 21 cm of textual records
    Federal Pacific Electric
    - Policies and Procedures (24-01), 1969 - 1973; F-11-1-18-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-21)
    - Reports - General (24-02), 1969 - 1974; F-11-1-18-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-21)
    - Insurance (24-17), 1972 - 1974; F-11-1-18-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-21)
    - Work Orders - General (24-22), 1971; F-11-1-18-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-21)
    - White Paper on Work Orders (24-22-24), 1973; F-11-1-18-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-21)
    - Boilers and Boiler Room (24-27), 1968 - 1975; F-11-1-18-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-21)
    - Boilers and Boiler Room (24-27), 1967 - 1975; F-11-1-18-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-21)
    - Change Orders (Boilers #4) (24-27-01), 1970 - 1971; F-11-1-18-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-21)
    - Boiler No.4 - General (24-27-02), 1969 - 1975; F-11-1-18-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-21)
    - Stores Section (24-29), 1971 - 1974; F-11-1-18-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-21)
    - Electrical Section (24-30), 1968 - 1974; F-11-1-18-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-21)
    - High Voltage Electrical System (24-30-01), 1968 - 1970; F-11-1-18-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-21)
    - Elevators (24-30-03), 1972 - 1975; F-11-1-18-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Federal Pacific Electric (24-30-06), 1971; F-11-1-18-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Papers Presented, Articles (24-39), 1969 - 1973; F-11-1-18-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Colour Specs for University (24-60), 1965; F-11-1-18-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Computerized Billing (24-90), 1971 - 1973; F-11-1-18-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - P.P. and P. - Brochure (24-92), 1971; F-11-1-18-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Policies and Procedures (30-01), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-18-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Policies and Procedures (30-01), 1978; F-11-1-18-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Insurance (30-13), 1976 - 1979; F-11-1-18-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Work Orders (30-14), 1977; F-11-1-18-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Safety and Planning - General (30-24), 1978; F-11-1-18-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Personnel (30-26), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-18-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Departmental Festivities (30-29), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-18-0-25 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Planned Preventive Maintenance System (30-32), 1977; F-11-1-18-0-26 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Data Bank (30-33), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-18-0-27 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Security (30-34), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-18-0-28 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
  - Students, 1970 - 1978; F-11-1-19; 4 cm of textual records
    Peak Publications Society; CJSF Radio
    - Campus radio (26-14), 1970 - 1975; F-11-1-19-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Peak Newspaper (80-02), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-19-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-60)
    - Residences - General Part A (82-01), 1974 - 1977; F-11-1-19-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-60)
    - Residences - General Part B (82-01), 1974 - 1977; F-11-1-19-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-60)
  - Buildings and grounds - general, 1965 - 1978; F-11-1-20; 13 cm of textual records
    MacMillan Bloedel
    - Channel 8, FM Antenna (CBC) (28-01), 1965 - 1974; F-11-1-20-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Weather Station (28-05), 1970; F-11-1-20-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Banks (28-06), 1968 - 1973; F-11-1-20-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Macmillan-Bloedel (28-10), 1969; F-11-1-20-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Client Architect Agreements (28-26), 1971 - 1975; F-11-1-20-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Trails (28-44), 1968 - 1973; F-11-1-20-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Construction - Project Management (28-30), 1969 - 1971; F-11-1-20-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Arboretum - Burnaby Mountain (28-58), 1970 - 1973; F-11-1-20-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Contractor's Liability Insurance (28-60), 1974; F-11-1-20-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Contracts (28-70), 1970; F-11-1-20-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Tree Nursery (28-74), 1970; F-11-1-20-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-22)
    - Water and Sewer System (28-80), 1970 - 1972; F-11-1-20-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-23)
    - Building Info Sheets (28-88), 1968 - 1978; F-11-1-20-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-23)
    - SFU Specs for New Building (28-90), 1971 - 1974; F-11-1-20-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-23)
    - Water Tower (Don Mills) (28-96), 1972; F-11-1-20-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-23)
    - Trails (32-03), 1975 - 1978; F-11-1-20-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Naheeno Park (32-04), 1975 - 1976; F-11-1-20-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
  - Barristers and solicitors, 1974 - 1978; F-11-1-21; 2 cm of textual records
    - Shrum, Liddle and Hebenton (122-02), 1974 - 1975; F-11-1-21-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-35)
    - Shrum, Liddle and Hebenton (24-01), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-21-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
  - Maintenance, 1968 - 1978; F-11-1-22; 3 cm of textual records
    - Fire Prevention and Inspections (100-08), 1968 - 1974; F-11-1-22-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-35)
    - Safety and Inspections (100-10), 1968 - 1974; F-11-1-22-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-35)
    - University reroofing and leaks (92-06), 1977 - 1978; F-11-1-22-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-61)
  - Long-range planning, 1972 - 1976; F-11-1-23; 1 cm of textual records
    - Long-range planning - general (22-01), 1972 - 1976; F-11-1-23-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-38)
  - Northside classroom block, 1966 - 1973; F-11-1-24; 38 cm of textual records
    - Northside Classroom Block] Change Order Correspondence (20-066-06-01), 1969 - 1970; F-11-1-24-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Northside Classroom Block] Specs (20-066034), 1968 - 1970; F-11-1-24-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Psychology (Classroom Complex) (20-066-48), 1969 - 1971; F-11-1-24-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Progress Certificates (Classroom Complex III) (40-02-01), 1968 - 1971; F-11-1-24-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-17)
    - Construction Progress Reports (CC) (40-04), 1968 - 1970; F-11-1-24-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-17)
    - Change Orders Part 1 (40-06), 1968 - 1969; F-11-1-24-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-17)
    - Change Orders Part 2 (40-06), 1968 - 1969; F-11-1-24-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-17)
    - Change Order Correspondence (40-06-01), 1970 - 1971; F-11-1-24-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-17)
    - Materials Testing (CC) (40-12), 1968 - 1970; F-11-1-24-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-18)
    - Contract Documents (CC) (40-16), 1968 - 1969; F-11-1-24-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-18)
    - Site Meetings (CC) (40-18), 1968 - 1970; F-11-1-24-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-18)
    - Concrete (Walkways, etc.), Tile (40-30), 1968 - 1971; F-11-1-24-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-18)
    - Leaks (40-36), 1968 - 1973; F-11-1-24-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-18)
    - Bids (40-38), 1968; F-11-1-24-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-18)
    - Revisions, Additions, Deletions, Extras, and Inspections (40-40), 1968 - 1971; F-11-1-24-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-18)
    - Clerk of Works Reports (40-42), 1968 - 1970; F-11-1-24-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-18)
    - Power and Electrical (40-44), 1969 - 1972; F-11-1-24-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-18)
    - Photographs and Drawings (40-50), 1968 - 1969; F-11-1-24-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-18)
    - Acoustic Design, Electronic Music Studio (40-54), 1966 - 1972; F-11-1-24-0-19 (Archival box - small 11-19)
    - Mechanical Room #4 (40-60), 1970 - 1971; F-11-1-24-0-20 (Archival box - small 11-19)
    - Completion Dates (40-62), 1970; F-11-1-24-0-21 (Archival box - small 11-19)
    - Addition to Classroom Block (40-64), 1969 - 1972; F-11-1-24-0-22 (Archival box - small 11-19)
    - Completion of Concourse (40-70), 1970 - 1971; F-11-1-24-0-23 (Archival box - small 11-19)
    - Final Settlements (40-72), 1970; F-11-1-24-0-24 (Archival box - small 11-19)
  - Adminstration building, 1963 - 1978; F-11-1-25; 21 cm of textual records
    - General (30), 1970 - 1972; F-11-1-25-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-23)
    - Progress Reports (30-01-01), 1969 - 1970; F-11-1-25-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-23)
    - Progress Certificates (30-04-01), 1970 - 1973; F-11-1-25-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-23)
    - Cost Estimates (30-01-02), 1969 - 1970; F-11-1-25-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-23)
    - Construction Contracts and Bonds (30-02), 1970 - 1971; F-11-1-25-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-23)
    - Fees (30-04-02), 1969 - 1971; F-11-1-25-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-23)
    - Change Orders (30-04-03), 1970 - 1972; F-11-1-25-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-23)
    - Change Order Correspondence Part 1 (30-05-01), 1970 - 1972; F-11-1-25-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-23)
    - Change Order Correspondence Part 2 (30-05-01), 1970 - 1972; F-11-1-25-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-23)
    - Site Meetings Minutes (30-06-01), 1970 - 1971; F-11-1-25-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-24)
    - Progress Claims (30-06-04), 1970 - 1971; F-11-1-25-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-24)
    - Materials Testing Reports (30-06-05), 1970 - 1971; F-11-1-25-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-24)
    - Heating, Ventilation, Boiler, Plumbing (30-09), 1963 - 1973; F-11-1-25-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-24)
    - Electrical (Conducts) (30-18), 1970 - 1972; F-11-1-25-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-24)
    - Flooring (30-30), 1971 - 1972; F-11-1-25-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-24)
    - Supply and Installation of Ride Through Generation Set (30-42), 1971 - 1973; F-11-1-25-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-24)
    - Computing Centre (34-03), 1976 - 1978; F-11-1-25-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Computing Renovations (34-03-01), 1978; F-11-1-25-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Contract Documents (34-03-02), 1978; F-11-1-25-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
    - Ancillary Services (34-04), 1976; F-11-1-25-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
  - Academic quadrangle, 1968 - 1978; F-11-1-26; 2 cm of textual records
    - Academic quadrangle - expenditures (32-02), 1968 - 1970; F-11-1-26-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-24)
    - Academic quadrangle - general (36-01), 1978; F-11-1-26-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-39)
  - B.C. Hydro - Systems Control Centre, 1968 - 1975; F-11-1-27; 1 cm of textual records
    BC Hydro
    - B.C. Hydro Systems Control Centre - general (34-01), 1968 - 1975; F-11-1-27-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-24)
  - Cafeterias, 1968 - 1978; F-11-1-28; 10 cm of textual records
    - Expenditures - East Concourse Cafe (36-02-01), F-11-1-28-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-25)
    - Change Orders - East Concourse Cafe (36-02-03), 1969 - 1974; F-11-1-28-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-25)
    - Landscaping - East Concourse Cafe (36-02-05), 1969; F-11-1-28-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-25)
    - Materials Testing - East Concourse Cafe (36-02-06), F-11-1-28-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-25)
    - Tender Docs - East Concourse Cafe (36-02-18), 1968; F-11-1-28-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-25)